Cuba's LPG tanker, Amelia, returned empty after Jamaica declined to load fuel following new U.S. sanctions that penalize countries supplying energy to Cuba.
So one, I just want to let y'all know that Jamaica is owned by the U.K.
So just know that.
Still, that's why they don't have control of their beaches.
But I also want to take this moment to tell you, Grenada, please remember that the airport is named the Maurice Bishop Airport because it was built out of a camaraderie between Maurice Bishop and Comandante Fidel Castro.
Just a little reminder there for you.
Never forget, Cuba, like Haiti, are one of only two Caribbean countries that successfully have gained their own independence.
And throughout that time, Cuba has faced sanctions while consistently being an integral element of elevation to the rest of the islands of the Caribbean.
We must never forget Cuba.
Viva la Cuba.
All right.
Happy Sunday.
Happy Independence.
You're damn rude, eh?